[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
I'm never going back to that life, Mama Yaya.
Are you happy?
-This is my life now. -Chiara.
This is the life I chose.
What do you mean "congratulations"?
Don't you remember?
Let's see who you're hiding, Sean.
anyone who tries to mess with our lives again.
It's time.
But what if Chiara still has unfinished business at La Concordat?
Could that be why someone still wants to reach out to her?
No, Chiara isn't like that. She's changed so much.
I've seen how happy she is.
How much she loves the life they've built here.
She wouldn't let anyone destroy that.
If she did have unfinished business,
she wouldn't be acting like this.
Chiara is efficient,
fast,
quiet.
Should I ask Chiara herself?
No.
I'm only asking for one promise.
I never stopped waiting
and preparing for this day.
The day our dreams would finally come true.
I've found a different dream.
I've built the life I want.
I did my part, Chiara.
It's time for you to do yours.
The first time I saw you, Chiara, I was shocked.
I got used to seeing violence in this mansion,
but you were different.
You never cried. You never complained.
You just silently took every hit and every beating.
Chiara.
My dear.
So,
I came here.
Then you came along.
I just wanted to take care of you.
Yaya,
Mama Yaya,
while you're here.
You know…
I guess that's what it is.
For now,
La Morte Bianca is the queen.
But one day,
you could be the Queen.
You too.
I didn't even understand what any of that meant.
And so much has changed.
I found a life I wanted to choose.
And this is what I want now, not that.
What do you think?
You think everything that happened in your life was just a coincidence?
No, Chiara.
There's a reason you're still alive.
There's a reason La Morte Bianca fell.
There's a reason you were left behind.
What are you saying?
I waited 20 years for you.
For 20 years, I prepared for this very moment.
No.
How?
How could you be so sure
that this day would come?
That I'd still keep our promise,
our plans?
I didn't make sure.
I prepared.
While you thought you were running away from the kingdom,
I was slowly preparing this for your return.
You know, sir, the timing is just suspicious.
Just a few days after Mikoy proposed to Chiara,
something like this suddenly came up.
I still haven't detected any high-risk foreign nationals
who entered the country this past week.
I think this person is Filipino.
There's something else you need to know.
When a leader is taken down,
someone always takes their place.
Our counterpart agencies have noticed something.
There have been more internal killings.
More families are disappearing.
And even their former allies
are suddenly disappearing off the map.
There really wasn't another woman, babe.
There really wasn't.
Okay, even if you…
even if you cut it off,
you can fry it, chop it up, make sisig out of it,
there really wasn't anyone!
There really wasn't. No one.
No, I mean…
That woman wasn't my ex.
She wasn't someone from my past either.
Okay, there really was nothing. She wasn't a one-night stand either.
There was nothing going on at all.
-Sisig? -Yes.
And so?
Something happened in my life that became the most complicated chapter
of my life, okay?
I was completely broken that day.
Then she suddenly came along.
It's just… She was like
a fairy godmother.
But without a wand.
She came into my life at the worst possible time.
She helped me.
She helped me get back on my feet.
That's all.
There was nothing romantic about it.
So,
a woman came into your life
when you were heartbroken?
And then,
she saved you?
Yes.
But
the way you're saying it makes it sound really bad.
It's not like that!
Because it really is bad!
But, okay, I met her abroad!
I met her abroad!
Alice.
Alice, Alice.
That day,
I thought my life was over.
But because of her, I found hope again.
So don't think that just because La Morte Bianca is gone
La Concordat is over.
That's not how these organizations work.
When one falls, someone takes their place.
And more often than not,
they're even more dangerous.
If someone is making a move around Mikoy and Chiara,
we can't rule out
that they're connected to La Concordat.
Continue the profile, okay?
Find what we're missing.
Stay on high alert for now.
No assumptions. We need facts.
And in the mafia,
the fight for the throne never truly ends.
So,
where is she now?
She went back to her hometown.
But
why did you have to make it so suspicious
just by talking to her?
And you even went as far as switching SIM cards.
Babe. You're an agent, right?
You know there are people who don't want to be traced.
So when I found out she was here, and she talked to me,
I immediately started thinking.
What if someone was monitoring my phone?
And I didn't want her to get dragged into it.
So I immediately bought a prepaid SIM.
Then after one call, I threw it straight in the trash.
Just a safety precaution.
I guess you're just being protective.
I really am protective of the people I love.
And you're one of them.
Let me make it up to you.
We confessed our feelings, then we got married.
So, are we officially together?
Confession,
fake wedding while drunk.
Does that count?
We can't just suddenly become boyfriend and girlfriend, right?
Or maybe we need to go on a honeymoon first?
Oh, Sofie, you're getting ahead of yourself again!
What's the proper message to send after a wedding?
Is there etiquette for that?
Okay.
No.
She might think I'm serious about marrying her.
Wait.
Am I serious?
Maybe he's just embarrassed, or maybe he was really just drunk.
No, whatever.
Oh, no. Oh, no, it sent!
Good thing I'm out of load.
Some information came in at the agency.
It's not verified yet,
so I can't give you the details.
But it's enough
for me to tell you to keep an eye on your surroundings for now.
Is this about Chiara and the others?
For now, I can't say yes, but I can't say no either.
I'm just keeping my promise.
Thank you.
And Mario, until we're sure,
let's just let them think it's only about the wedding.
Okay, you're right.
I'll handle things here.
Fire! There's a fire!
-Fire! -Mario!
-Mario! -Mario!
-Mario, there's a fire! -Mario!
-Come on, hurry. -Let's go.
Mario!
Straight ahead!
How are you?
Unfortunately, still alive.
Sometimes, that's enough.
When we lose someone,
we only have two choices.
We can choose to follow them,
or we can live with a purpose.
Even now,
I feel like everything is my fault.
I couldn't save her.
If only I had been braver.
I wish Alice were still with me.
I know what it's like to lose someone.
But you know what's even more painful?
Living your life without doing anything.
For the rest of your life,
we slowly give up.
But they,
they just keep living.
They just keep hurting people.
What else can I do?
A lot.
Don't waste your pain.
Use it.
Make it your reason to fight.
And if I want
to find whoever did this to Alice and me?
You don't have to do this alone.
I'll be with you.
Let's help each other.
While you seek justice,
I'll help you learn to live again.
Let's fill the emptiness with new reasons
to live and fight.
-because of the severity of his injuries. -Injuries?
How is he?
We still don't know if there was a fight
or if he violated any rules inside.
Not far.
This is starting to feel like a security agency!
How are you related to him?
-He's my brother. -All right. You're good, bro-in-law!
Could there be a reason for it?
They're not like this before.
Here's the thing.
Do you think if Victor escaped, he'd come back?
I'm just worried. Something's not right.
And we both know that Senator Quintin is up to something dirty.
I was just thinking.
What if we don't go through with the wedding?